 const data = {
    1:{
        question : "What is React?",
        options : ["A Javscript library","A programming language","An operating system","A Javascript framework"],
        answer: "A Javscript library"
    },
    2:{
        question:"Which of the following is used to pass data to a component in React?",
        options:["useEffect","State","Props","Dom"],
        answer: "Props"
    },
    3:{
        question:"What is the purpose of react router in react?",
        options:["Managing Http requests","Navigation and Routing","Authentication","Connecting components"],
        answer: "Navigation and Routing"
    },
    4:{
        question:"What is JSX stands for in React?",
        options:["Javascript Extension","Java XML","Javascript XML","JSON Extension"],
        answer: "Javascript XML"
    },
    5:{
        question:"What is the purpose of react Fragments?",
        options:["To create new element","To group multiple elements","To define reusable elements","To add extra node"],
        answer: "To group multiple elements"
    },
    6:{
        question:"What does Redux provide for managing the state?",
        options:["Centralized state management","Remote state management","Store","Private state management"],
        answer: "Centralized state management"
    },
    7:{
        question:"What is the use of virtual Dom in react?",
        options:["To Manipulate HTML DOM","To reduce HTTP requests","To batch state updates","To reduce direct DOM manipulation"],
        answer: "To reduce direct DOM manipulation"
    },
    8:{
        question:"What is the role of ProtoTypes in React?",
        options:["To define state","To define HTML Tree","To define dataType of Props","To define dataType of variables"],
        answer: "To define dataType of Props"
    },
    9:{
        question:"What is the purpose of Key attribute?",
        options:["For styling list","For changing list","For uniquely identifying list items","For creating a list"],
        answer: "For uniquely identifying list items"
    },
    10:{
        question:"What is the significance of react virtual dom",
        options:["Improving reconciliation","Replacement for DOM","Server side rendering","Replcement for Redux"],
        answer: "Improving reconciliation"
    },

}

export default data;